Blake Neely

Creative full-stack developer with experience in Javascript, React, Node.js, Express and many more. Skilled in designing, developing and maintaining multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of modern technologies. 139 Strathmore Way Hendersonville, TN 37075 615.431.1422 blake@neelystudio.com neelystudio.com linkedin.com/in/blakeneely/

EXPERIENCE

Neely Studio — *Developer and Founder*

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT

- Construct/improve branding and marketing strategy to increase conversion rates
- Build and deploy websites from ground up based on customer input
- · Sales, marketing, and branding for business

Verizon — Solutions Manager

MARCH 2015 - PRESENT

- Develop system for directing customer shopping patterns and trends
- Train team members on systems and SalesForce
- Organize and present daily standups and weekly meetings

Verizon — Solutions Specialist

SEPTEMBER 2010 - MARCH 2015

- Improve, innovate and communicate sales processes to meet demanding goals
- Manage financial and sales data primarily through CSV files and Excel
- Communicate to upper management and my team

EDUCATION

Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN — Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp

JULY 2019 - JANUARY 2020

Middle Tennessee State University, Murfreesboro, TN — *B.B.A. Marketing*

2001 - 2006

CODE

Github — *github.com/blakeneely*

Holds most of my side projects, most of my code is proprietary to the customers I assist.

TECH

Languages: HTML/CSS, Javascript

Front-end Frameworks: React, Bootstrap, Handlebars js,

Back-end Frameworks: Express.js

Databases: mongoDB, mySQL, Firebase

Other: Node.js, Git, Bash, Axios, jQuery, Cheerio, AJAX, Shopify, Procreate, Sketch

SIDE PROJECTS

Binge: A movie search and save to watch later web app. Search by movie or actor, read the description or watch the trailer and add the movie to your Binge list. Come back anytime to view and edit your Binge list!

Weather: Ever wonder what the weather is like anywhere in the world? Effortlessly search and in this React based app to find out!

Google Book Search: Similar to Binge but with books! Search to find your favorite book and add them to your bookshelf.

<u>TechFeed:</u> Grab and save top articles from today's top tech websites.